https://www.tecan.com/terms-of-use-privacy-and-cookies-policy?p=tab--1

Tecan uses cookies to improve our website. By continuing to browse our website, you accept our cookie policy.
History
Quality policy (ISO)
i-control™
[more]
Liquid-liquid extraction
Which smart sample prep solution best fits your application?
i-control™
[more]
Cavro Omni Flex
Cavro Mini Sample Processor (MSP)
Cavro Omni Robot
Cavro Robotic Sample Processor (RSP)
Pump technologies
Air Displacement Pipettor
Cavro Air Displacement Pipettor (ADP)
Diaphragm Pumps
Cavro MiniWash Pump (MW)
Peristaltic Pumps
Cavro Smart Peristaltic Pump (SP)
Terms of Use, Privacy Policy and Cookies Policy
Thank you for visiting Tecan’s Website. Your access to and use of this Website is subject to the Terms of Use and all applicable laws. By accessing and browsing this Website, you accept, without limitation or qualification, these Terms of Use and acknowledge that any other agreements regarding the use of this Website between you and Tecan Trading AG are superseded and of no force or effect.
We take your rights as a data subject very seriously.
Data subject request
Questionnaire
Terms of Use
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Cookies Policy
tab--1
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Cookies Policy
***************************************************************************************
***************************************************************************************
Tab 01 / Terms of Use
***************************************************************************************
***************************************************************************************
Terms of Use
While great efforts were made to ensure accurate and up-to-date information on this website, Tecan makes no representations or warranties whatsoever, express or implied, as to the content of this website and the products and services described therein, including, without limitation, with respect to accuracy, completeness, non-infringement, merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, or availability, and Tecan disclaims any liability for losses or damages of any kind, including losses or damages resulting from the use of information taken from this website or from the transmission or downloading of computer viruses.
Tecan may make improvements and/or changes to any product(s), product specification or service(s) described in this site at any time without notice. Tecan does not guarantee that any product or service described in this site will be continuously available. The information on our site is periodically updated. The information contained on this website does not constitute an offer for products or services.
Tecan cannot be held responsible for third party content that is published on Tecan's website or cited references.
Investors must not rely on information provided on this website for investment decisions.
Application for Biopharma
The products in this section are Research Use Only. Not for use in human clinical diagnostics or in vitro diagnostic procedures.
Applications for Diagnostics and Liquid Handling and Robotics
Not all applications, options and products in this section have been cleared for clinical use in all countries. If you have questions or concerns please contact your local sales office for specific information.
Microplate Readers, Washers and Microarray products
PowerScanner™, LS Reloaded™ and HS 4800™ Pro and HS 400™ Pro hybridization stations are Research Use Only/scientific instrumentation. Not for use in clinical diagnostics. The other products in this section are Class 1, 510(k) exempt devices for general purpose use.
Components
All products described in this section are components that will be further integrated in a system.
Consumables
Not all products in this section can be used in the clinical environment. If you have questions or concerns please contact your local sales office for specific information.
Trademarks
List of trademarks
Copyright
Unless otherwise stated, the copyright and similar rights in the contents of this site, including but not limited to all text, designs and images appearing herein, are copyrighted works owned by Tecan Trading AG.
You are permitted to print or download extracts from the material of this web site for your personal use only so long as any copy or other reproduction includes the above copyright notice. None of the material of this site may be used for any commercial or public use. No material appearing on this site may be disseminated in any form, either electronic or non-electronic, nor included in any retrieval system or service without prior written permission of Tecan. For further information please please feel free to contact us.
***************************************************************************************
***************************************************************************************
Tab 02 / Privacy Policy
***************************************************************************************
***************************************************************************************
Privacy Policy
Tecan is a leading global provider of laboratory instruments and solutions in biopharmaceuticals, forensics and clinical diagnostics. The company specializes in the development, production and distribution of automated workflow solutions for laboratories in the life sciences sector. As an original equipment manufacturer (OEM), Tecan is also a leader in developing and manufacturing OEM instruments and components that are then distributed by partner companies.
The Tecan Group of Companies collects personal data about you. Tecan as the Controller processes your personal data in compliance with the provisions under the Swiss Data Protection Act ("DPA") and General Data Protection Regulation ("GDPR"), as amended from time to time (collectively "Regulation"). This Data Protection Policy ("Policy") explains how we use any personal data we collect about you.
Tecan may modify this Privacy Policy. The most up-to-date version of this Privacy Policy will always be published on our website.
Table of contents (Topics)
What Personal Data do we collect?
Personal Data is any information relating to you or that we can otherwise link to you. The Personal Data we collect includes your name, postal address, e-mail address, phone and fax number, company name, company structure, job title and business affiliations. Where you visit one of our Web-Shops, Personal Data may also comprise financial data (such as e.g. credit card details) which we need to execute the transaction(s) you request.
How do we collect your Personal Data?
We collect Personal Data that you voluntarily provide to us, for example when (i) registering with us in order to place an order for products or services; (ii.) communicating with us via e-mail or other channels, (iii) when signing up for or asking us to send you newsletters or other (marketing) materials and (iv) when signing up for an event.
As further described in our Cookies Policy, we use cookies and similar technologies (e.g. web beacons, pixels and tags and device identifiers) to recognize you and/or your device(s) when visiting the Tecan website. We also allow some others to use cookies as described in our Cookies Policy. You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools.
In some cases your Personal Data has been obtained or supplemented by information retrieved from other sources, including searches via publically available search engines, sector-specific newsletters, social media and your employer’s website, for the purpose of confirming your current professional position.
How do we use your Personal Data?
We use the Personal Data we collect for communication purposes, including: (i) to send you newsletters  and other information about Tecan, our products and our services; (ii) to send you invitations to events, training sessions, conferences and lectures; and (iii) to maintain our list of contacts.
In addition, we use Personal Data in order to sell our products and services to you and provide after-sales services.
Why do we process your Personal Data and on what legal basis?
As set out above we process your Personal Data for communication purposes. We rely on our legitimate interests in maintaining business relationships and communicating with you as a business contact, about Tecan's activities and events. We consider that our legitimate interests are in compliance with the Regulation and your legal rights and freedoms. You can request to be removed from our distribution lists at any time. Upon such request, we will cease to send you such communication and invitations.
Furthermore, we process your Personal Data where necessary in order to perform a contract or to meet legal requirements.
Where is your Personal Data stored? / Where is your Personal Data transferred?
Tecan is a Swiss company which stores your Personal Data on servers in Switzerland and on servers of the Microsoft Corporation in The Netherlands and in Ireland.
We may disclose your Personal Data to other Tecan affiliates worldwide that agree to treat it in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Personal data may also be transferred to third parties who act for or on our behalf, for further processing in accordance with the purpose(s) for which the data were originally collected or may otherwise be lawfully processed, such as services delivery, evaluating the usefulness of this website, marketing, data management or technical support. These third parties (“Processors”), which partly are located outside the European Union, have contracted with us to only use Personal Data for the agreed upon purpose, and not to sell your personal information to third parties, and not to disclose it to third parties except as may be required by law, as permitted by us or as stated herein.
We do not make your Personal Data available to any third party other than Processors.
How long do we keep your Personal Data?
Your Personal Data will be saved for the specified purposes mentioned above for as long as you are a business contact to us or longer periods where required for legal and/or regulatory reasons.
Data Security
Tecan has implemented appropriate technical and organisational security measures to help protect your Personal Data against loss and to safeguard against access by unauthorised persons.
Your Rights
You have the right to know what Personal Data we process about you and may request a copy. You are also entitled to have incorrect Personal Data about you corrected and you may in some cases ask us to delete your Personal Data. You can also object to certain Personal Data about you being processed and request that processing of your Personal Data be limited. Please note that the limitation or deletion of your Personal Data may mean we will be unable to provide the communications and invitations described above. You also have the right to receive your Personal Data in a machine-readable format and have the data transferred to another party responsible for data processing. Any of those requests concerning those rights can be addressed through the Questionnaire at the top of this page. If you disagree with how we process your Personal Data, you are also entitled to report this to the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner (FDPIC) and/or to the competent supervisory authorities in the EU.
How to contact us
If you have any questions about how we process your Personal Data, please feel free to contact us through the Questionnaire at the top of this page.
***************************************************************************************
***************************************************************************************
Tab 03 / Cookies Policy
***************************************************************************************
***************************************************************************************
Cookies Policy
The Tecan Group of Companies ("Tecan" or “we”) uses cookies on its Website. By using the Website, you consent to the use of cookies.
Tecan’s Cookies Policy explains what cookies are, how we use cookies, your choices regarding cookies and further information about cookies.
What are cookies
Cookies are small pieces of text sent to your web browser by a website you visit. A cookie file is stored in your web browser and allows the Service or a third-party to recognize you and make your next visit easier and the Service more useful to you.
Cookies can be "persistent" or "session" cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your personal computer or mobile device when you go offline, while session cookies are deleted as soon as you close your web browser.
How Tecan uses cookies
When you use and access the Service, Tecan or third parties may place a number of cookies files in your web browser.
Tecan uses cookies for the following purposes:
Site preferences cookies
In order to provide you with a great experience on this site we provide the functionality to set your preferences for how this site runs when you use it. In order to remember your preferences we need to set cookies so that this information can be called whenever you interact with a page is affected by your preferences.
Analytics cookies
We may use analytics cookies to track information how the Service is used so that we can make improvements. We may also use analytics cookies to test new pages, features or new functionality of the Service to see how our users react to them.
Orders processing cookies
This site offers e-commerce or payment facilities and some cookies are essential to ensure that your order is remembered between pages so that we can process it properly.
Forms cookies
When you submit data to through a form such as those found on contact pages or comment forms cookies may be set to remember your user details for future correspondence.
Subscription cookies
This site offers newsletter or email subscription services and cookies may be used to remember if you are already registered and whether to show certain notifications which might only be valid to subscribed/unsubscribed users.
Third-party cookies
In addition to our own cookies, we may also use various third-parties cookies to report usage statistics of the Service.
What are your choices regarding cookies
If you'd like to delete or disable cookies or instruct your web browser to delete or refuse cookies, please visit the help pages of your web browser.
Please note, however, that if you delete or disable cookies or refuse to accept them, you might not be able to use all of the features we offer, you may not be able to store your preferences, and some of our pages might not display properly.
For the Chrome web browser, please visit this page from Google.
For the Internet Explorer web browser, please visit this page from Microsoft.
For the Firefox web browser, please visit this page from Mozilla.
For the Safari web browser, please visit this page from Apple.
For any other web browser, please visit your web browser's official web pages.
More information
Hopefully this has answered any question you had. If there is something that you aren't sure whether you need or not it's usually safer to leave cookies enabled in case it does interact with one of the features you use on our site.
However if you are still looking for more information please feel free to contact us through the Questionnaire at the top of this page.
Follow Tecan
empty cart | close cart
Your cart
Your cart is empty.
Update totals
Total:
Get a quote close form
|delete item
